

My Contact

mfahmifadh@gmail.com

(+62 857-7265-2563

Depok

in linkedin.com/in/mfahmifadh

Hard Skill

- HTML 5, Bootstrap 4, CSS
- PHP, Javascript, .Net Core 5
- Framework Code Igniter, Laravel, Jquery
- Database MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQL Server
- Canva, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere

Soft Skill

- Adaptability
- Communication
- Fast Learner
- Professionalism
- Responsibility
- Teamwork

Project Activity

- (2022) Created Web Application Ikatan Alumni SMAN 2 Padang Angkatan 1992
- (2019) Created Web Application Tanaman Obat Keluarga for Community Dedication using Framework Laravel 5.6

Certification

 Certificate of Competence Programming and Software Development (Web Developer)

National Professional Certification Board (BNSP) (Oct 2021 - Oct 2024)

MUHAMMAD FAHMI F

Full Stack Developer

About Me

I am an applied graduate student in 2022 majoring in Informatics and Computer Engineering at the Jakarta State Polytechnic. I am someone who is adaptable, responsive, responsible, likes challenges, likes to learn new things and has good problem solving skills. I have professional and part time experience in the creation and development of a website. I also have an interest in system analysis, and quality assurance.

Educational History

2018 - 2022 Jakarta State Polytechnic

Informatics and Computer Engineering

2015 - 2018 Taruna Bhakti Vocational School

Software Engineering

Professional Experience

Biro Umum Kemenkes RI

Jan, 22 - Present | Web Developer Contract

- Created Warehouse Management Information System
- Created Administration Manajemen System for Wisma Sukajadi Bandung.
- · Created Centralized office operational management system

Sep, 21 - Dec, 21 | Web Developer Intern

 Created a performance supervision information system, building management services using Laravel framework.

PT. Bank Negara Indonesia

Jan, 22 - Sep, 22 | IT Business Partner Intern

- Created Business Solution Design Document
- Helped receive and notes getting request from other division for IT product development

Jun, 21 - Dec, 21 | Backend Developer

 Created API used used .Net Core 5 and database SQL Server for Information System Monitoring Project at BNI

PT. National Data Integrator

May, 18 - Jul, 18 | Query Analys

• Manage query data using the syndi application

Organization

2021 Vice Project Officer ITechno Cup 2021

2019 - 2020 Head of Department Education & Technology

2018 - 2019 Staff of Department Education & Technology

Informatics Engineering Student Association and Computers Organizing an Evaluation Meeting for the Computer and Informatics Engineering Department Student Study Group